A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records FA248
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1972-2001; 2 (Reel 15, Frame 203)
  - Programs, 1976-2001; 1 (Reel 15, Frame 204)
    - Lyon College, Break the Mold, 93-247, Year Four-Year Five, 1997-1999 (Reel 68, Frame 740)
    - Magazine School District, Magazine High School, 93-10, 1993-1994 (Reel 68, Frame 924)
    - Magazine School District, Magazine Elementary School, 93-202, 1993-1994 (Reel 68, Frame 956)
    - Magnolia Public Schools, 94-10, 1994 (Reel 68, Frame 1003)
    - Magnolia Public Schools, 95-123, 1995-1996 (Reel 68, Frame 1036)
    - Mallalieu Black Community Developers, Incorporated, 93-227, 1993-1996 (Reel 68, Frame 1081)
    - Malvern Public Schools, 88-159, 1988-1989 (Reel 69, Frame 1)
    - Mammoth Spring School District, 93-63, 1993-1994 (Reel 69, Frame 18)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation, 83-324, 1983-1984 (Reel 69, Frame 50)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation/Arkansas Department of Human Services, 84-398, 1984-1985 (Reel 69, Frame 76)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation, 85-513, 1985-1987 (Reel 69, Frame 106)
    - Marion School District, Phelix Elementary School, 89-18, 1989-1990 (Reel 69, Frame 124)
    - Marion School District, "S.T.A.R.S.", 89-97, 1989-1990 (Reel 69, Frame 141)
    - Marion School District, 90-26, 1990-1991 (Reel 69, Frame 158)
    - Marion School District, 91-87, 1991-1992 (Reel 69, Frame 231)
    - Marion School District, Marion Middle School, 92-91, 1992-1993 (Reel 69, Frame 260)
    - Marshall, Linda, Professional Services Agreement, 1986-1988 (Reel 69, Frame 319)
    - Matrix IV, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1992-1994 (Reel 69, Frame 331)
    - McGehee School District, 94-11, 1994 (Reel 69, Frame 471)
    - McGuigan, Dermot, Professional Services Agreement, 1981 (Reel 69, Frame 509)
    - McKenzie, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1981-1987 (Reel 69, Frame 530)
    - McKnight, John, Professional Services Agreement, 1990-1991 (Reel 69, Frame 560)
    - Meadowcreek Project, Incorporated, 80-2003, 1980 (Reel 69, Frame 564)
    - Meadowcreek Project, Incorporated, 81-1002, 1981 (Reel 69, Frame 580)
    - Meadowcreek Project, Incorporated, 82-260, 1982-1983 (Reel 69, Frame 596)
    - Meadowcreek Project, Incorporated, 84-397, 1984-1985 (Reel 69, Frame 623)
    - Meadowcreek Project, Incorporated, 85-481, 1985-1986 (Reel 69, Frame 650)
    - Meadowcreek Project, Incorporated, 86-579, 1986-1987 (Reel 69, Frame 673)
    - Meadowcreek Project, Incorporated, 86-612, 1986-1987 (Reel 69, Frame 698)
    - Meadowcreek Project, Incorporated, 88-44, 1988-1991 (Reel 69, Frame 723)
    - Mena Public Schools, 88-20, 1988-1989 (Reel 69, Frame 839)
    - Meretazon, Ari S., Professional Services Agreement, 1990-1994 (Reel 69, Frame 856)
    - Michelli, Nicholas, Professional Services Agreement, 1996 (Reel 69, Frame 867)
    - Miller, Jerry, Professional Services Agreement, 1988 (Reel 69, Frame 875)
    - Mission Projects, Incorporated, (in behalf of Total Health Services, Incorporated), 80-2038, 1980-1981 (Reel 69, Frame 879)
    - Mississippi Action for Community Education, Blues Festival, 82-280, 1982 (Reel 69, Frame 893)
    - Mississippi County Arkansas Economic Opportunity Commission, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1997 (Reel 69, Frame 908)
    - Mitchell, James, Professional Services Agreement, 1990 (Reel 69, Frame 948)
    - Mitchell, Ruth, Professional Services Agreement, 1996 (Reel 69, Frame 956)
    - Monticello School District, City Park Elementary School, 89-80, 1989 (Reel 69, Frame 962)
    - Monticello School District, 92-150, 1992-1993 (Reel 69, Frame 975)
    - Monticello School District, 94-61, 1994-1995 (Reel 69, Frame 1015)
    - Monticello School District, 95-153, 1995-1996 (Reel 69, Frame 1052)
    - Moon, Tonya, Professional Services Agreement, 1990 (Reel 69, Frame 1102)
    - Morgan, Mark, Professional Services Agreement, 1990-1994 (Reel 69, Frame 1136)
    - Morris Booker Memorial College, 81-1003, 1981 (Reel 69, Frame 1143)
    - Morris Booker Memorial College, 82-268, 1982-1983 (Reel 69, Frame 1158)
    - Morris Booker Memorial College, 83-325, 1983 (Reel 69, Frame 1172)
    - Morris Booker Memorial College, 83-345, 1983-1984 (Reel 69, Frame 1193)
    - Mount Holly Public Schools, 88-108, 1988-1989 (Reel 69, Frame 1216)
    - Mount Saint Mary Academy, 87-746, 1987-1988 (Reel 69, Frame 1235)
    - Mountain Home Public Schools, Mountain Junior High School, 89-8, 1989-1990 (Reel 69, Frame 1254)
    - Mountain Home Public Schools, 94-21, 1994-1995 (Reel 70, Frame 1)
    - Mountain Home Public Schools, 94-83, 1994-1995 (Reel 70, Frame 40)
    - Mountain View School District, 94-143, 1994-1995 (Reel 70, Frame 80)
    - Murfreesboro Community Foundation, 91-136, 1991-1992 (Reel 70, Frame 135)
    - Murfreesboro Public Schools, 88-6, 1988 (Reel 70, Frame 226)
    - Murfreesboro Public Schools, 96-11, 1996 (Reel 70, Frame 243)
    - Murphy, Patrick, Professional Services Agreement, 1990 (Reel 70, Frame 306)
    - Murphy, Sara, Professional Services Agreement, 1983-1992 (Reel 70, Frame 314)
    - Museum of Science and History, Solar Life Celebration, 79-1020, 1979 (Reel 70, Frame 592)
    - My House, Incorporated, 95-187, 1995-2000 (Reel 70, Frame 603)
    - NAACP Fairshare Economic Development Program, National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 90-130, 1989-1993 (Reel 70, Frame 744)
    - NAACP Legal Defense Fund, Incorporated, National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 79-1018, 1980 (Reel 70, Frame 861)
    - Nashville Public Schools, 87-802, 1987-1989 (Reel 70, Frame 871)
    - Nashville Public Schools, 87-837, 1987-1988 (Reel 70, Frame 885)
    - Nashville Public Schools, 89-39, 1989 (Reel 70, Frame 900)
    - Nashville Public Schools, 94-173, 1994-1995 (Reel 70, Frame 915)
    - National Association of State Board of Education, 87-762, 1987-1988 (Reel 70, Frame 957)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Incorporated, NCCJ, 90-129, Original Proposal-Year One, 1989-1993 (Reel 70, Frame 986)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Incorporated, NCCJ, 90-129, Year Two-Year Three, 1992-1994 (Reel 71, Frame 1)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Incorporated, NCCJ, Jewish History, 92-86, 1992 (Reel 71, Frame 243)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Incorporated, NCCJ, 93-86, 1993-1996 (Reel 71, Frame 371)
    - The National Faculty, 92-193, Original Proposal-Year One, 1992-1994 (Reel 71, Frame 612)
    - The National Faculty, 92-193, Year Two, 1993-1996 (Reel 71, Frame 859)
    - National Home Caring Council, Home Healthcare, 81-240, 1981 (Reel 71, Frame 1019)
    - National Home Caring Council, Home Healthcare, 82-294, 1982-1984 (Reel 71, Frame 1040)
    - National Urban League, 95-139, 1995-1996 (Reel 71, Frame 1061)
    - National Wildlife Federation, Weyerhaeuser Monitoring, 80-178, 1980-1983 (Reel 72, Frame 1)
    - Native American Coalition of Arkansas, 95-138, 1995-1997 (Reel 72, Frame 88)
    - The Nature Conservancy, "Overflow Bottoms" PRI, 80-3000, 1980-1981 (Reel 72, Frame 165)
    - The Nature Conservancy, Model Land Conservation Program, 81-247, 1981-1983 (Reel 72, Frame 187)
    - Neighborhood Housing Services, Incorporated, 79-1021, 1979-1980 (Reel 72, Frame 213)
    - Nemo Vista Public Schools, Nemo Vista High School, 91-40, 1991-1992 (Reel 72, Frame 244)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, 89-81, 1989-1990 (Reel 72, Frame 280)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, Nettleton High/Interim School, 90-57, 1990-1991 (Reel 72, Frame 299)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, University Heights Elementary School, 91-45, 1991-1992 (Reel 72, Frame 344)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, 91-97, 1991-1992 (Reel 72, Frame 383)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, 92-128, 1992-1995 (Reel 72, Frame 425)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, Fox Meadow Elementary School, 93-14, 1993 (Reel 72, Frame 467)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, Nettleton High School, 93-57, 1993-1994 (Reel 72, Frame 501)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, Fox Meadow Elementary School, 93-140, 1993-1994 (Reel 72, Frame 542)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, Nettleton High School, 93-195, 1993-1994 (Reel 72, Frame 581)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, School Improvement, 93-206, 1993-1999 (Reel 72, Frame 618)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, 94-37, 1993-1994 (Reel 72, Frame 822)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, 94-46, 1994 (Reel 72, Frame 865)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, 94-181, 1994-1995 (Reel 72, Frame 903)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, 95-5, 1995 (Reel 72, Frame 940)
    - Nettleton Public Schools, 95-126, 1995 (Reel 72, Frame 981)
    - Nevada School District, 92-10, 1992 (Reel 72, Frame 1004)
    - Nevada School District, Nevada Elementary School, 93-16, 1992-1993 (Reel 72, Frame 1037)
    - Nevada School District, 95-17, 1994-1996 (Reel 72, Frame 1064)
    - New Earth Health Services, Incorporated, 81-1003, 1981 (Reel 72, Frame 1112)
    - New Horizon Church and Its Ministries, Incorporated, 94-104, 1994-1995 (Reel 72, Frame 1135)
    - New Horizon Church and Its Ministries, Incorporated/New Horizon Development Corporation, 95-83, 1995-1996 (Reel 73, Frame 1)
    - Newark School District, 90-123, 1990-1991 (Reel 73, Frame 94)
    - Newark School District, Oil Trough Elementary School, 93-64, 1993-1994 (Reel 73, Frame 148)
    - Newton County Housing Council, 94-191, 1994-1998 (Reel 73, Frame 184)
    - Newton County Resource Council, NCRC, 89-117, 1989-1993 (Reel 73, Frame 330)
    - Newton County Resource Council, NCRC, 91-153, 1991-1993 (Reel 73, Frame 409)
    - Newton County Resource Council, NCRC, Affordable Housing, 91-163, 1991-1994 (Reel 73, Frame 435)
    - Newton County Resource Council, NCRC, 93-228, Original Proposal-Year One, 1993-1996 (Reel 73, Frame 687)
    - Newton County Resource Council, NCRC, 93-228, Year Two-Year Four, 1994-1998 (Reel 73, Frame 940)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, Formerly Human Service Providers Association of Arkansas, 84-405, 1984-1985 (Reel 74, Frame 1)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 85-480, 1985-1987 (Reel 74, Frame 27)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, Database, 85-526, 1985-1986 (Reel 74, Frame 47)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 86-664, 1986-1988 (Reel 74, Frame 59)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 86-706, 1986-1988 (Reel 74, Frame 70)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 87-830, 1987-1988 (Reel 74, Frame 97)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 87-853, 1988 (Reel 74, Frame 112)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 88-138, 1988-1989 (Reel 74, Frame 133)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 88-138, Year Three, 1989-1990 (Reel 74, Frame 152)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 89-124, 1990-1991 (Reel 74, Frame 163)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 90-128, 1985-1991 (Reel 74, Frame 171)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 91-158, 1991-1993 (Reel 74, Frame 357)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated/Arkansas Grantseekers Horizon, 91-167, 1989-1992 (Reel 74, Frame 433)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1992-1996 (Reel 74, Frame 496)
      Grant number: 92-139
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 92-139, Year One-Year Four, 1992-1998 (Reel 74, Frame 656)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 95-171, 1995-1999 (Reel 74, Frame 859)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, 97-1, 1997-1999 (Reel 74, Frame 1064)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, Financial Management Workshops, Professional Services Agreement, 1985-1998 (Reel 75, Frame 1)
    - NonProfit Resources, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1996-1997 (Reel 75, Frame 160)
    - Norfork Schools, 89-10, 1989 (Reel 75, Frame 226)
    - Norfork Schools, 90-106, 1990-1991 (Reel 75, Frame 246)
    - North Crossett Elementary School, 85-545, 1985-1986 (Reel 75, Frame 317)
    - North Garland County Youth Center, Incorporated, 93-148, 1993-1994 (Reel 75, Frame 339)
    - North Garland County Youth Center, Incorporated, 95-96, 1995-2000 (Reel 75, Frame 3.84)
    - North Little Rock Public Schools, 85-538, 1985-1986 (Reel 75, Frame 693)
    - North Little Rock Public Schools, Ridgeroad Junior High School, 87-683, 1987 (Reel 75, Frame 708)
    - North Little Rock Public Schools, Indian Hills Elementary School, 87-777, 1987-1988 (Reel 75, Frame 724)
    - North Little Rock Public Schools, Bellwood Elementary School, 88-127, 1988-1989 (Reel 75, Frame 741)
    - North Little Rock Public Schools, West Campus High School, 91-123, 1991-1992 (Reel 75, Frame 767)
    - North Little Rock Public Schools, West Campus High School, 92-109, 1992-1994 (Reel 75, Frame 812)
    - North Little Rock Public Schools, Ridgeroad Junior High School, School Improvement, 93-214, 1993-1995 (Reel 75, Frame 873)
    - North Little Rock Public Schools, Lakewood Middle School, School Improvement, 93-215, 1993-1996 (Reel 75, Frame 960)
    - Northcentral Arkansas Education Service Center, 95-100, 1995-1997 (Reel 75, Frame 1132)
    - Northeast Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 87-846, 1987-1988 (Reel 75, Frame 1210)
    - Northeast Arkansas School District, Baldwin Elementary School, 89-84, 1989-1990 (Reel 76, Frame 1)
    - Northeast Arkansas School District, Baldwin Elementary School, 90-12, 1989-1990 (Reel 76, Frame 19)
    - Northeast Arkansas School District, 92-8, 1991-1992 (Reel 76, Frame 78)
    - Northeast Arkansas School District, 92-164, 1992-1994 (Reel 76, Frame 122)
    - Northeast Arkansas School District, 93-11, 1992-1993 (Reel 76, Frame 178)
    - Northeast Arkansas School District, 93-110, 1993-1994 (Reel 76, Frame 207)
    - Northeast Arkansas School District, 94-126, 1994 (Reel 76, Frame 259)
    - Northside Redevelopment Corporation, Incorporated, 91-108, 1991-1992 (Reel 76, Frame 305)
    - Northside Redevelopment Corporation, Incorporated, 92-202, 1992-1993 (Reel 76, Frame 364)
    - Northwest Arkansas Education Service Cooperative, 95-102, 1995-1998 (Reel 76, Frame 394)
    - Northwest Arkansas Rape Crisis, 93-149, 1993-1994 (Reel 76, Frame 483)
    - Oasis Resources, Incorporated, 92-195, 1992-1995 (Reel 76, Frame 523)
    - Oasis Resources, Incorporated, 93-152, 1993-1994 (Reel 76, Frame 773)
    - Office of Rural Advocacy, Professional Services Agreement, 1993 (Reel 76, Frame 823)
    - Okolona Love Council, 88-103, 1988-1989 (Reel 76, Frame 827)
    - Ola Public Schools, 91-113, 1991-1994 (Reel 76, Frame 845)
    - Ola Public Schools, Ola Elementary School, 91-127, 1991-1992 (Reel 76, Frame 877)
    - Olive Garden Development Corporation, 94-109, 1994-1996 (Reel 76, Frame 926)
    - Ouachita Baptist University, Red River Region, 83-319, 1983 (Reel 76, Frame 968)
    - Ouachita County Youth Aid, Incorporated, 93-89, 1993-1994 (Reel 76, Frame 996)
    - Ouachita County Youth Aid, Incorporated, 94-199, Original Proposal-Year One, 1994-1998 (Reel 77, Frame 1)
    - Ouachita County Youth Aid, Incorporated, 94-199, Year Two-Year Three, 1995-1998 (Reel 77, Frame 327)
    - Ouachita Girl Scout Council, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1992-1994 (Reel 77, Frame 576)
      Grant number: 92-191
    - Ouachita Girl Scout Council, 92-191, Year One-Year Three, 1992-1996 (Reel 77, Frame 713)
    - Ouachita Public Schools, Ouachita Elementary School, 91-42, 1991-1992 (Reel 77, Frame 815)
    - Ouachita Public Schools, 95-57, 1994-1995 (Reel 77, Frame 848)
    - Our Lady of Good Counsel, 89-38, 1989-1990 (Reel 77, Frame 892)
    - Our Lady of Holy Souls, 88-77, 1988-1989 (Reel 77, Frame 910)
    - Ozan Inghram/Iron Mountain, Neighborhood Development Corporation, 92-43, 1992-1993 (Reel 77, Frame 941)
    - Ozan Inghram/Iron Mountain, Neighborhood Development Corporation, 93-150, 1993-1994 (Reel 77, Frame 1058)
    - Ozan Inghram/Iron Mountain, Neighborhood Development Corporation, 93-235, 1993-1998 (Reel 78, Frame 1)
    - Ozark Action, Incorporated, 78-1016, 1978 (Reel 78, Frame 246)
    - Ozark Action, Incorporated, 78-1017, 1978 (Reel 78, Frame 254)
    - Ozark Alternative Crop Education Training and Promotion Association, 92-133, 1992-1993 (Reel 78, Frame 264)
    - Ozark Foothills Resource Conservation and Development Project, Incorporated, 93-232, 1993-1994 (Reel 78, Frame 325)
    - Ozark Foothills Resource Conservation and Development Project, Incorporated, 94-155, 1994-1995 (Reel 78, Frame 383)
    - Ozark Institute, 86-663, 1986-1988 (Reel 78, Frame 420)
    - Ozark Legal Services, Incorporated, Videotapes, 80-180, 1980-1986 (Reel 78, Frame 447)
    - Ozark Legal Services, Incorporated, Ozark Elders, 80-2035, 1980-1981 (Reel 78, Frame 470)
    - Ozark Recycling Enterprise, Incorporated, 90-61, 1990-1991 (Reel 78, Frame 484)
    - Ozark Recycling Enterprise, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1989-1990 (Reel 78, Frame 812)
    - Ozark Regional Land Trust, 87-738, 1987-1988 (Reel 78, Frame 820)
    - Ozark Regional Land Trust, 88-54, 1988-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 840)
    - Ozark Returned Peace Corps Volunteers, 1991-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 912)
    - Ozarks Unlimited Resources Cooperative, 85-514, 1985-1986 (Reel 78, Frame 935)
    - Palestine-Wheatley School District, 93-55, 1993-1994 (Reel 78, Frame 952)
    - Pangburn Public Schools, Pangburn Elementary School, 91-38, 1991-1992 (Reel 78, Frame 1004)
    - Pankey Community Improvement Association, Incorporated, 93-159, 1993-1994 (Reel 78, Frame 1046)
    - The Parent Center, 84-412, 1984-1985 (Reel 78, Frame 1083)
    - The Parent Center, 85-507, 1985-1986 (Reel 78, Frame 1124)
    - The Parent Center, 86-686, 1986-1988 (Reel 78, Frame 1150)
    - Paris Public Schools, 92-205, 1992-1994 (Reel 78, Frame 1173)
    - Paris Public Schools, 93-49, 1993-1994 (Reel 79, Frame 1)
    - Paris Public Schools, 93-106, 1993-1996 (Reel 79, Frame 46)
    - Paris Public Schools, 94-16, 1994-1995 (Reel 79, Frame 92)
    - Parkers Chapel School District, 94-135, 1994-1995 (Reel 79, Frame 128)
    - Parkin Public Schools, 93-167, 1993-1994 (Reel 79, Frame 173)
    - Partnership of the Future, Incorporated, 86-689, 1986-1988 (Reel 79, Frame 224)
    - Pathfinder Schools, Incorporated, 82-269, 1982 (Reel 79, Frame 249)
    - Pea Ridge Schools, 88-99, 1988-1989 (Reel 79, Frame 279)
    - Pea Ridge Schools, 88-158, 1988-1989 (Reel 79, Frame 294)
    - Pea Ridge Schools, 89-49, 1989-1990 (Reel 79, Frame 306)
    - Peace Links Worldwide, Incorporated, 83-340, 1983-1984 (Reel 79, Frame 321)
    - Peace Links Worldwide, Incorporated, 84-423, 1984-1985 (Reel 79, Frame 348)
    - Peace Links Worldwide, Incorporated, 85-506, 1985-1986 (Reel 79, Frame 377)
    - Peace Links Worldwide, Incorporated, 86-622, 1986-1987 (Reel 79, Frame 411)
    - Peace Links Worldwide, Incorporated, 87-786, 1987-1988 (Reel 79, Frame 438)
    - Peace Links Worldwide, Incorporated, 88-83, 1988-1989 (Reel 79, Frame 469)
    - PEDCO, Incorporated, Presbyterian Economic Development Corporation, Incorporated, Minority Business, 79-1022, 1979-1980 (Reel 79, Frame 490)
    - PEDCO, Incorporated, Presbyterian Economic Development Corporation, Incorporated, 80-2036, 1980-1982 (Reel 79, Frame 522)
    - The People's Institute for Survival and Beyond, Professional Services Agreement, 1993 (Reel 79, Frame 550)
    - The People's Institute for Survival and Beyond, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1995 (Reel 79, Frame 554)
    - Perryville Public Schools, 86-639, 1986-1987 (Reel 79, Frame 569)
    - Perryville Public Schools, Gifted and Talented, 87-818, 1987-1988 (Reel 79, Frame 598)
    - Perryville Public Schools, 88-123, 1988-1990 (Reel 79, Frame 622)
    - Person to Person Citizen Advocacy, Incorporated, 94-67, 1994-1998 (Reel 79, Frame 646)
    - Philander Smith College, 84-464, 1985-1986 (Reel 79, Frame 704)
    - Philander Smith College, 85-560, 1986 (Reel 79, Frame 748)
    - Philander Smith College, 86-702, 1986-1987 (Reel 79, Frame 781)
    - Philander Smith College, PRI Loan, 91-130, 1991-1993 (Reel 79, Frame 828)
    - Pine Bluff Downtown Development, Incorporated, 92-196, 1992-1994 (Reel 79, Frame 963)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, 87-775, 1987-1988 (Reel 79, Frame 1010)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, Pine Bluff High School, 90-17, 1990-1991 (Reel 79, Frame 1026)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, Indiana Street School, 90-44, 1990-1991 (Reel 79, Frame 1075)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, Carver Elementary School, 91-26, 1991-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 1129)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, Greenville Elementary School, 91-41, 1991-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 1166)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, 91-85, 1991-1992 (Reel 79, Frame 1202)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, Southeast Junior High School, 91-124, 1991-1992 (Reel 80, Frame 1)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, 93-12, 1993 (Reel 80, Frame 40)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, George Washington Carver Elementary School, 94-89, 1994-1997 (Reel 80, Frame 84)
    - Pine Bluff Public Schools, 95-60, 1995-1996 (Reel 80, Frame 229)
    - Pitts, Barbara A., Professional Services Agreement, 1993-1994 (Reel 80, Frame 282)
    - Plainview-Rover School System, 89-69, 1989-1990 (Reel 80, Frame 336)
    - Plainview-Rover School System, 89-94, 1989-1990 (Reel 80, Frame 354)
    - Plainview-Rover School System, Plainview Elementary School, 91-23, 1991 (Reel 80, Frame 370)
    - Planned Parenthood of Arkansas, Incorporated, 88-137, 1988-1990 (Reel 80, Frame 408)
    - Policy Studies Associates, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1994 (Reel 80, Frame 441)
    - Policy Studies Associates, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1995 (Reel 80, Frame 675)
    - Pope County 4-H Association, Incorporated, 94-159, 1994-1995 (Reel 80, Frame 730)
    - Potts, Jody, Professional Services Agreement, 1987 (Reel 80, Frame 776)
    - Pottsville School District, 95-63, 1995-1996 (Reel 80, Frame 781)
    - Powers, Jennifer, Professional Services Agreement, 1987 (Reel 80, Frame 822)
    - Prairie Grove Public Schools, 93-66, 1993-1994 (Reel 80, Frame 829)
    - Prentice, Mary, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1997 (Reel 80, Frame 857)
    - Presbyterian Urban Council, Peace Links Worldwide, Incorporated, 82-281, 1982 (Reel 80, Frame 895)
    - Presbytery of Arkansas, Agriculture Marketing, 86-605, 1986-1987 (Reel 80, Frame 916)
    - Presbytery of Arkansas, 87-790, 1987-1989 (Reel 80, Frame 943)
    - Prescott School District, 94-171, 1994-1995 (Reel 80, Frame 964)
    - Prescott School District, 95-158, 1995 (Reel 80, Frame 1023)
    - PTA Arkansas Congress, 93-75, 1993-1994 (Reel 80, Frame 1061)
    - PTA Arkansas Congress, 94-164, 1994-1997 (Reel 81, Frame 1)
    - Pulaski Activity Center, 86-607, 1986-1987 (Reel 81, Frame 158)
    - Pulaski Activity Center, 87-784, 1987-1988 (Reel 81, Frame 188)
    - Pulaski Activity Center, 88-89, 1988-1990 (Reel 81, Frame 209)
    - Pulaski County, Professional Services Agreement, 1994 (Reel 81, Frame 225)
    - Pulaski County Circuit Court, 92-25, 1992 (Reel 81, Frame 248)
    - Pulaski County Council on Aging, Incorporated, 80-2037, 1980-1982 (Reel 81, Frame 343)
    - Pulaski County Educational Cooperative, 86-675, 1986-1987 (Reel 81, Frame 365)
    - Pulaski County Educational Cooperative, 87-760, 1987-1988 (Reel 81, Frame 392)
    - Pulaski County Quorum Court, Pulaski County Quorum Reorganization Study, 91-137, 1991-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 408)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 85-565, 1985-1987 (Reel 81, Frame 664)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 86-714, 1986-1988 (Reel 81, Frame 695)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 87-692, 1987 (Reel 81, Frame 725)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 87-778, 1987-1988 (Reel 81, Frame 737)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 88-21, 1988-1989 (Reel 81, Frame 756)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 88-160, 1988-1989 (Reel 81, Frame 770)